You know, stay here for a weekend,
see what it's like.
(Bernadette:)- Your mom would be okay with that?
- Sure, she would.
(Howard:)Ma, do you mind if Bernadette
stays here this weekend?
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Hey, if she's
willing to give the milk away for free...
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)...who am I to say no?
(Howard:)See? She's good with it.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Frankly, after all
your sleepovers with the little brown boy...
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)...a girl is a big relief.
All these years, I've been so wrong.
(Sheldon:)The tinier the train,
the more concentrated the fun.
(Penny:)You're a brain scientist.
Can you explain why a brilliant man
Iikes playing with toy trains?
(Amy:)Not without cutting his head open, no.
(Amy:)How about making my eyes
Iike Cleopatra?